prosperitybankusa.com 2019-06-23

# Prosperity Bank - Privacy Notice

This notice applies to individuals (and their legal representatives) who obtain Prosperity Bank® financial products or services on both an ongoing and occasional basis, which are to be used primarily for personal, family or household purposes.

## PRIVACY POLICY

Click Privacy Notice for the Prosperity Bank Privacy Notice.

## INTERNET PRIVACY POLICY

When you visit our website at [www.prosperitybankusa.com](http://www.prosperitybankusa.com/), to view any pages, read product information, or use our online calculators and other tools, you do so without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information. While we do not collect identifying information about visitors to our site, we do use software to collect information for the strict purpose of tracking activity on our site. This allows us to better understand how many people visit us and which pages and features are most popular. The information we collect and store is:

  * The name of your internet service provider
  * The website that referred you to us (if any)
  * The date and time the pages were accessed
  * The page or pages you requested

There are instances where you may elect to provide us with personal information. For example, if you fill out one of our feedback or request forms or send e-mail, you are transmitting the information that applies to you in the form of a message. This will typically include information like your name, mailing address, e-mail address, the kind of request you are making, and any other information necessary to fulfill your request. You only transmit personally identifying information that you enter yourself. This information cannot be collected unless you specifically elect to send it to us. This information is used internally only for the purpose of fulfilling the request or for contacting you directly and is not given or sold to any other business or organization.

When you submit personally identifying information via one of our feedback or application forms, that information is also encrypted, or scrambled, by your browser before it is transmitted back to our website. This effectively prevents anyone from intercepting and reading any personal information about you. **Note that this encryption does not take place if you send us e-mail, but only when you use your Web browser with one of our forms.**

The Prosperity Bank® website is not currently targeted or marketed to children.
